where are the people bro
it hits me
uh we go on this
these are the multi-function leggings
I will say
it was me my love
against mouths and gossip
on this side
we have a coconut shell that could be thrown in the garbage
and we decided to reuse
it's mass
a different talent ne
put that of the time
what is your
and
your
foot
ok ok ok
the time has come to decide who is the winner
whether they are satisfied or not
yes what's hardest about people is going up
pick up the microphone
and show your art
express yourself
be the box is that
is you being yourself
so congratulations to each of you from the bottom of my heart
I want to call the four finalists
of the talent show here
i wanted to ask some questions and understand
for us to decide the prize
with the prize I will pay my school benefit
stopped investing in sustainable and conceptual fashion
I learned with twisting
it was through my mother's phone
i so wanted to have a good phone that was for
have more engagement with my work
try to see a bag out
with this award
we want
expand our joinery and visual arts workshop
to welcome young people from the mafalala neighborhood
that most are lost in drugs
and we want to use art to transform mafalala
very good
palms to everyone
applause to everyone for
social impact
and the impact of transformation
congratulations brother
the prize is yours
this is a project i want you to send
a legacy
a lot for mafalala
for the people here contributing
makes art alive
continue
collab with wonderful people like them too
congratulations
thank you
congratulations brother
palms palms
palms people thank you very much for being here
tamo together
I love you
na cure